Riki is sleeping right in front of me...
This is such a wonderful dream.
Wafuu!!
Kud, calm down! It's me!
Why are Riki and I sleeping in the same bed?!
Please... be gentle with me.
With what?!
As your girlfriend, I'm elated that you'd risk your wellbeing by sneaking into the girls' dorm for me,
but I am not quite prepared for all this yet.
Hold on! Y-You don't remember anything?
Wafu!
Have we crossed that line already?
That's not what I meant.
You really don't remember why I stayed the night?
Wafu...?
Wow, a home run!
That puts us five points ahead! No way they're catching up now!
The ball's gone quite far.
Nice home run there, Masato!
You saw that, Riki? That's out-of-the-park muscles for you!
Muscles yay yaaay!!
Muscles, muscles!!
Muscles yay yaaay!
Hmm? Oh?
Whoa...
What the heck...?
Apparently the boys' dorm was flooded by a water pipe that was damaged by a stray baseball.
Dammit! Who would do such a thing?!
It was yoooou!!
I'm so sorryyyy!
You've gotta be kidding...
Where should we sleep now...?
Kanata-san, what will the boys do during summer vacation?
As far as this goes, we can't really tell them to sleep in the classrooms or the gym.
We'll have the boys stay in the empty rooms in the girls' dorm.
Ohhhh!
Ehhhh?
We'll assign the rooms by lottery.
There!
No. 4! Who's got No. 4?!
It's gotta be Riki, right?
Sorry.
Why does my lot say "Rin"?
You're the seed, Natsume-kun.
It wouldn't be bad to spend some family time with your sister during the break now, would it?
I see. Sounds like a plan.
I don't wanna!
Senpai, what does "better luck next time" mean?
Oh, Naoe-kun, you drew that one, huh?
We don't actually have enough empty rooms left in the girls' dorm.
There you have it.
You'll be staying in the home economics clubroom.
Riki!!
Are you really going to stay in the clubroom?
Yeah, I drew the bad lot, so it seems that way.
U-Umm, actually...
I'm still...
...looking for a roommate.
So, that's why...!
Would you like to be my roommate?
Thanks, but a girl and boy staying in the same room...
If siblings are fine, I don't see a problem if a girlfriend and boyfriend share a room, either!
I think there is.
Riki is so rational.
Um, but...
That was actually just an excuse.
To tell the truth, I just want to spend more time with you...
Is that not okay...?
And that's how we ended up staying in your room together.
That rings a bell...
But how did we end up sleeping in the same bed?
Kudryavka, what was that scream just now about?
K-K-Kanata-san!
Open up.
I'm changing right now, so wait just a moment, please!
Kudryavka, why are you answering the door wearing that?
I'd feel bad to keep you waiting...
Eek!
I-I'm changing right now...!
C-Could you please come back later...?
There are guys staying in the dorms now, so think about the way you dress.
There's a guy in this room right now, not just the dorms!
I-It's okay! Riki isn't in the room right now!
Of course he isn't. What are you talking about?
What would happen if Riki was here?
All the guys staying in the girls' dorm would have to take collective responsibility and leave.
They'd have to sleep in the classrooms for the summer instead.
Why would you ask something like that, Kudryavka?
B-Because Riki... isn't here right now.
Well, of course he isn't.
Now hurry up and get changed.
You didn't bring much.
It's summer, so I don't have to worry about bulky clothes.
Where should I put my underwear?
You can put them in the top drawe —
Wait up, Riki!
Wafuuuu!!
Don't look!
I'm not looking!
I'm not thinking anything like, "I didn't expect them to be so small" or "You've got some pretty mature stuff in here"!
Kudryavka-kun, may I have a moment?
Kurugaya-san!
Why, good morning!
Is there something you need?
Yep. I'm here to return the panties I borrowed when I visited the other day.
When did you borrow those?!
Kurugaya-san, what are you doing...?
I'm putting them back where I got them.
Hmm, it's summer all right.
Wafu?
We've been caught...
I-I'm sure Kurugaya-san will keep it a secret!
Kuu-chan, I'm coming in!
Komari-san, what's the matter?
Well, when I came to hang out the other day — waah!
I see. I guess it's summer.
Kamikita-san found out, too.
It's fine! I'm sure it's all going to be okay!
It sure is summer, isn't it?
Kud, let's go get breakfast!
Sounds good! We won't have to hide anything with everyone there!
My my, summer's in the air.
Everyone found out...
Wafu...
Riki!!
Have you been lonely?
Do you miss my muscles?!
It hurts, Masato!
Riki, you can come stay in our room.
We'll have our muscles futon laid out and ready!
With Kengo on the bottom, me on top,
and you right in the middle!
Please elaborate.
I can tell you're worried about your childhood friend...
Huh?
...but it's senseless of you to make light of his determination.
But...
Besides, more so than anything...
It's summer, after all.
It's summer.
Yep, it's summer.
Yes, it is.
It's senseless because it's summer?
That seems to be the case.
Pokey.
Shut up, you baldy.
Saigusa-san, is that a new prank of yours?
I made a static generator for my research project!
I see, so it's a prank.
It's science!
Oh yeah, we need to work on our independent research.
What are you going to do, Masato?
A growth record of my muscles, of course!
Don't make it sound like you're recording the growth rate of morning glories...
What about you, Kud?
I've already decided!
That's a rocket, isn't it?
Huh?
Ryachka, been doing well?
Long time no see, Himuro-san!
This is Himuro-san. She's visiting from our sister school during the summer for her research.
I'm Yuuki Himuro, president of the sister school's science club.
You know her?
Yes, she was my roommate while I was in Tevua!
That's quite the interesting project you're working on.
Yes!
My summer research project is going to be on water rockets!
Sorry for the wait!
Did you make this yourself, Kuu-chan?
Yes!
This is the first time I've made one,
so there's probably lots of room for improvement!
That's amazing.
Now we just need to use this to pump in air.
Couldn't we just use a compressor?
It's getting... harder and harder...
It's like doing isometrics.
Thank you very much, Inohara-san!
Looks to be ready for launch!
On the launch, okay!
Starting countdown!
T-minus!
Ignition!
That was amazing, Kud!
It flew that far with just water and air!
Yep, yep.
This was nothing more than craftwork.
I'm going to record data and keep experimenting to make it go further.
In that case, you should start with the wings' shape.
If you shape them like screws,
you can make the rocket spin, which will stabilize its trajectory.
A rocket launching into the blue summer sky, soaring among white clouds.
That's youth.
Let's all launch our own water rockets.
The one who emerges victorious in the end...
...will be given the title "Rocket King"!
Mission start!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Noooooo!
Wooow!
You're so good at this, Haru-chan!
Rin-chan, do your best!
It's hot...
Stop complaining and get a move on.
Hm?
W-Waaah!
My rockets!
Ah...
Yoh! Hah! Yah!
Wafu!
Now you won't drop them anymore.
Thank you very much.
You mentioned rockets just now.
Are you making water rockets with them?
How'd you know, Onee-chan?
Why, we're actually going to make rockets ourselves!
All of you? Amazing!
You must all be really good friends!
I don't have friends like that,
so I have to make them by myself...
My name is Noumi Kudryavka.
Would you tell me your name?
Shiina... Arizuki...
Shiina-san, we're friends now.
It's up to you, but would you like to make water rockets with us?
Yes!
Wow! Amazing!
These are our welcome cookies for Himuro-san and Shiina-chan!
Can I eat these?
This many will be a total cakewalk!
It's all soda, though?
Kengo, let's see which of us can down more of these!
Seems it's time for me to put you in your place.
Aghhh! My eyes!
My eyeeeeeees!
You brought that on yourself!
This is fun!
Now then, let's all make rockets out of the empty bottles!
Would shaping carbon nanotube like a bottle be cheating?
That's against the rules.
Carbon nanotube?
You make real rockets with it.
Real rockets?!
Yep!
Shiina-san, why do you want to make water rockets?
I want to become an astronaut!
Wafu!
My dream's to become a kosmonavt, too!
Also, my mother is a kosmonavt.
She's in the International Space Station right now!
Kud-san?
Don't worry, it's nothing.
Let's get back to work!
Okay, who's going to launch theirs first?
Yes, right here!
This rocket was jointly developed by Anego and me!
The Sexy Anego!
There's a picture on the rocket,
but this doesn't have anything to do with Kamikita-san, right?
Yep, yep.
It's one of my most prized photos.
You'll get to see Komari-kun in quite the embarrassing situation when the rocket is launched.
Ehhh?! When did you take such a picture?!
Huu! Huu!
Masato!
Yeah!
Ignition!
Wait up...!
Oh no, with how far it's flown, I can't see
Komari-kun's unbecoming appearance.
Don't look at it!
Strelka, don't fetch it!
Okay, next up!
Well then, here's the Naoe, made by Komari-san and me.
Why me?
Inohara-san, if you would, please.
Leave it to me!
Once it is launched, the photos of Naoe-san and Kyousuke-san will turn into ones where they're hugging each other.
Ehhhh?!
Wafu?!
I shopped it.
Ignition.
Belka, wait up!
It went farther than the Saigusa-Kurugaya team's.
Looks like we're up next.
Yeah...
Chest!
Fungaaaargh!
You have to launch them with water and air...
...so that's against the rules.
What?!
No waaaaaay!
You idiots.
Whoa! Pwapapopopeh?!
Do we have to use water and air?
All right! Next up, it's Riki, Noumi, and Shiina!
Yes! Okay! Yep!
Kud-san, can I become an astronaut?
Becoming a kosmonavt is a big dream.
But as long as you don't give up, you'll get there for sure!
Is that so?
Yep, I believe so!
As long as you don't give up...
Kud, it's all done!
Yes!
On the launch, okay!
Countdown!
Ignition!
When it comes to finding Polaris, my mom is a bit strange.
She'd start from the Summer Triangle.
If you put Altair of Aquila on the other side of the line connecting Vega of Lyra and Deneb of Cygnus,
that's where you'll find Polaris.
Is something the matter?
You've been looking at me for a while.
I was just thinking about how much you love your mom.
Mom...
Riki, could you listen to me for a little?
Sure.
My mom is a really amazing person.
I admired her... and she was my goal.
My mom has been a kosmonavt for as long as I can remember,
and she has always cheerfully told me the importance of going into space.
The reason I wanted to go to space...
The reason I wanted to become a kosmonavt was because
I wanted to see the same things my mom did.
I wanted to find out that the things she said she enjoyed are actually fun myself.
That was my dream.
But that was a really difficult road to follow.
The further I went, the farther away it felt like my mom was.
Before I knew it, I had stopped in my tracks.
I ran away from my mom.
I didn't have the confidence to fulfill her expectations and ran away from Tevua.
It was just that, a dream.
I wanted to keep at it and become a kosmonavt, thinking that would somehow justify it.
I think being able to talk to someone about your dreams is pretty impressive on its own.
Riki...
That makes me want to keep cheering you on by your side.
Thank you... very much.
Um... is it okay if I cast a good-luck charm?
A charm?
It's a charm for tying people who treasure each other together.
We draw our coat of arms on each other, and they turn into stronger bonds and oaths.
Kud?!
T-This is very embarrassing... and also very important and serious...
Will you marry me?
M-Ma-Marry?! Like tying the knot?
We're still in school, so I'm not trying to ask for something that ambitious yet,
but I have about the same determination and resolve...
Okay, I got it.
Let's do it.
Mnh.
Wafu!
Please don't move.
Sorry.
My coat of arms is filled with curvy waves and mountains...
My mom told me they were gears.
Gears?
I want to be a good set of gears to you.
Mm...
Wafu...
Kud, don't move.
I'm very... sorry.
But...
This is embarrassing...
It tickles...
What kind of pattern are you drawing on me?
Trees, I guess?
They'll always be there around you, protecting you from all sorts of things.
Riki...
I'll be able to do anything as long as Riki's with me.
As long as Riki is there, that's where I belong...
...no matter where...
Kud, wake up.
Wafu?
Mmm... Kud...
Even in your dream, you're there right next to me.
Riki's sleeping right in front of me...
This is such a wonderful dream.
Morning, Kud.
Good morning, Riki.
It's pretty quiet.
What happened to everyone?
That's right, everyone went home.
I've been...
...alone with Riki this entire summer.
Riki, let's go get breakfast!
Oh yeah, the cafeteria staff aren't here.
Why don't I make breakfast for you, then?
Really?
Yes, just leave it to me!
I'll come get you once I'm done, so just hang around in my room until then!
Mm... wafu.
I'm making miso soup for Riki...
It's like we're newlyweds!
Are you just going to keep running away?
Himuro-san, you're a strong person,
so there's no way you'll understand how I feel.
I'm just trying to be strong, nothing more,
and I just come off as strong to you as a result.
Which is why, for how strong I am, I can remain here.
You've noticed, haven't you?
That this place is closed off.
Still going to repeat it all?
Kyousuke-san said something similar...
And now... Himuro-san... you're telling me the same thing...
It just means you want someone to tell you.
As long as Riki's with me, I don't need anything else!
That's all I need!
As long as Riki's with me...
As long as he's there...
Riki, breakfast's ready.
Riki...?
Riki! Riki!
Riki?
Riki!
Riki!!
N-No way...
I've always known...
This is a convenient world where everything works out.
A misguided paradise that I created.
I wanted to become stronger, even if just within this world.
If I could get just a little better... become just a bit stronger...
...perhaps I could take flight one day, too...
No... I'm sure that won't ever happen...
I'll only ever be like this...
Kud...!
Riki...?
Kud!
I'll come help you right now!
Riki...? Why?
I'll get these chains off right away!
Riki! Please stop...!
I'm fine with this...
I remember everything... I know what happened...
I've already given up because of the accident on the field trip.
It was a relief to have it all come to an end even if I didn't run away.
But I wanted you, whom I love the most, to be saved,
so I prayed over and over...
That's why, just knowing you got out fine was more than enough for me...
I'm not fine with it!
We were going to rescue everyone!
Kud... I wanted to become someone who's strong.
I wanted to understand what it meant to be strong.
I wanted the strength to protect somebody.
And... I learned from everybody.
I learned what it meant from you!
That's why I was able to wake up.
I'm... not strong...
I repeated all of this over and over.
I kept repeating everything over and over and over because it worked out for me...
...and kept running away.
And I'll repeat it again.
I'm weak. I'll only ever be bound by these chains...
I'll only ever be a Kudryavka who can't take flight.
No, you're not.
You've been looking for a way to get stronger this whole time.
Riki...
It's okay. You already know what that means.
I already do...?
Let's go, Kud!
Riki, where are we going?!
You can fly anywhere as long as you wish for it!
Your feelings will reach anywhere!
Kuu-chan, I've filled it up with water!
Komari-san?!
It's all set and ready to go.
Nishizono-san?!
You can count on our calculations for the wings!
The wind's calm. It's the perfect time for launch.
Saigusa-san! Kurugaya-san!
Inohara-san! Miyazawa-san!
We're leaving the rest to you!
Just ten more pumps!
Noumi!
Here's a new mission for you!
Surpass yourself.
Kud, do your best!
You can do it!
Kyousuke-san...
Rin-san...
Now, Kud!
The mission's started!
Yes!
10... 9...
8... 7...
6...
You've been running away this whole time.
Can you really get any stronger?
5...!
All you've been doing is repeating this comfy world of yours.
4...!
You, the Kudryavka who's bound by chains and cannot fly.
I want to get stronger! I want to fly!
If you're going to do it, stick it out to the very end.
Don't just have all the fun yourself. Let me join in, too.
Ryachka, believe in yourself.
Himuro-san...
Himuro-san!
As long as you don't give up, your wish will surely come true!
Everyone...
3...!
2...!
1...
Kud, hang in there!
Kud?!
Kud!
Kunya.
1...!
Kud!
Yes!
Riki?!
Riki, wait up!
I can't get stronger by myself!
I can't fly if you aren't there next to me!
Riki...!
Kud...
Kud!
Kud!!
Ri...ki...?
Is Riki on the other side of the sky...?
Has he been watching over me this whole time...?
That's right... Riki and I are connected.
Riki... I'm coming to see you now.
On the launch, okay!
Starting countdown!
T-minus
9, 8, 7, 6, 5!
Those chains represent my weakness.
The weakness of seeking strength.
They may appear to be connections, but they're actually rejections.
I have friends who are there for me.
Whenever I'm feeling lonely or in trouble, they're always there for me.
And Riki has always been there to support me as well.
2! 1!
Ignition!
Riki...?
Riki...
Kud!
Did Kuu-chan wake up?!
Little Kud!
Are you feeling okay?!
Kudryavka-kun!
Noumi-san.
Are you okay?!
Noumi!
Morning, Kud.
Good morning, everyone.
Kuu-chan!
Kud!
Hurray! Hurray!
After that long, long dream, I finally managed to wake up.
I wanted to save Riki, but he saved me in the end...
I never knew about this place.
I knew I wanted to come here with you as soon as I found it.
You can see all kinds of stars here when it gets dark.
If you don't mind, would you like to come stargazing some time?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Riki, would you mind listening to me about two things?
Two things?
The first is a question I have.
What do you think strength actually is?
I think you've already found that answer yourself.
I don't quite understand it yet.
I don't think you're strong just because you're not weak...
I think it's just understanding what it means to be weak.
Wafu...?
It's the ability to acknowledge you are weak and take even just one step further.
That's what I think it means to be strong.
I see.
How philosophical.
Hehe.
What's the other thing?
The second thing is something I wanted to tell you.
I'm going to work hard to become a kosmonavt.
I think there's going to be a tough road ahead,
and I am bound to lose heart over and over,
but I still want to make that my goal.
So you've made your decision.
Yep!
U-Umm...
Is it okay if I add just one more thing?
Riki...
I love you!