Riki's just a few inches away from me.
I hope this dream never ends.
Wafu!
Kud, calm down! It's me!
Why are Riki and I sleeping in the same bed?!
Please be gentle with me.
Come again?
The girlfriend in me is super happy that you'd
risk sneaking into the girls' dorm for me,
but this is all just moving so fast.
Hold on! Y-You don't remember anything?
Wafu!
Have we crossed that line already?
That's not what I meant.
You really don't remember why I stayed the night?
Wafu?
Wow, a home run!
That puts us five points ahead!
The game's in the bag now!
The ball has gone quite far.
Nice home run there, Masato!
See that, Riki?
Those are the muscles of a mega slugger!
Muscles, yay yay!
Muscles, muscles!
Oh?
Whoa...
What the heck?
It would seem the boys' dorm has been flooded
by a pipe burst from a runaway baseball.
Damn the luck! Who would do such a thing?
It was you!
I'm so sorry!
You've gotta be kidding.
Where are we gonna sleep now?
Kanata, what will the boys do during summer vacation?
It's true it wouldn't be fair to ask them
to sleep in the classrooms or the gym.
The boys will have to stay
in the empty rooms in the girls' dorm.
We'll assign the rooms by lottery.
There!
No. 4! Who's got No. 4?!
It's gotta be Riki, right?
Sorry.
Why does my lot say "Rin"?
You're the seed, Natsume.
It wouldn't be bad to spend some family time
with your sister during the break, now would it?
I see. Fine by me.
I don't wanna!
Hey, what does "better luck next time" mean?
Oh, Naoe, you drew that one, huh?
We don't actually have enough
rooms free in the girls' dorm.
There you have it.
You'll be staying in the home ec. room.
Riki!
Are you really going to stay in the clubroom?
Yeah, I drew the short straw, so it seems that way.
U-Um, actually...
The thing is...
I'm still...
looking for a roommate.
So, that's why...
Would you like to be my roommate?
Thanks, but a girl and boy
staying in the same room—
If siblings can do it,
I don't see why a couple can't, too!
Well, I think I can.
Riki is so rational.
Well, um...
That was actually just an excuse.
I really just want to spend more time with you, is all.
Am I asking too much?
And that's how the two of us
ended up staying in your room.
Th-That rings a bell.
Though I'm not sure how
we ended up in the same bed.
Kudryavka, what was that
scream just now about?
K-K-Kanata!
Open up.
I'm changing, so give me a second, please!
Kudryavka, why are you answering the door like that?
I'd feel bad to keep you waiting.
I-I'm trying to change!
Could you please come back later?
There are guys staying in the dorms now,
so think about the way you dress.
Forget the dorms, there's a guy
in this room right now!
I-It's okay! Riki isn't in the room right now!
Of course he isn't. Where did that come from?
And what if he were here?
All the guys staying in the girls' dorm
would be held at fault and forced to leave.
They'd have to sleep in the classrooms
for the summer instead.
Why would you ask something like that, Kudryavka?
B-Because Riki isn't in here right now.
Well, of course he isn't.
Now hurry up and get changed.
You didn't bring much.
It's summer, so I can dress light.
Where should I put my underwear?
You can put them in the top drawe—
Wait up, Riki!
Wafu!
Don't look!
I'm not looking!
I'm totally not thinking "Huh, they're pretty small"
or "You've got some sexy stuff in here."
Kudryavka, may I have a moment?
Kurugaya!
Why, good morning!
Is there something you need?
Yep. I'm here to return the panties I borrowed
when I visited the other day.
When did you borrow those?!
Kurugaya, what are you doing?
I'm putting them back where I got them.
It's summer all right.
Wafu?
That didn't stay a secret long.
I-I'm sure Kurugaya will keep it to herself!
Ku, I'm coming in!
Komari, what's the matter?
Well, when I came to hang out the other day—
I see. I guess it's summer.
Kamikita found out, too.
It's fine! I'm sure it's all going to be okay!
It sure is summer, isn't it?
Kud, let's go get breakfast!
Sounds good! There's nothing to hide
if we're out in public!
My my, summer's in the air.
Looks like the cat's out of the bag.
Wafu.
Riki!
Have you been lonely?
Do you miss my muscles?!
Easy, Masato!
Riki, you can come stay in our room.
We'll have our muscles sandwich
primed and ready!
With Kengo on the bottom, me on top,
and you right in the middle!
Please, tell me more.
I can tell you're worried about your childhood friend,
but it's senseless of you to
make light of his determination.
But...
Besides, more so than anything...
It's summer, after all.
Yup, yup. It's summer.
Totally summer.
Yes, it is.
It's senseless because it's summer?
That seems to be the case.
Pokey.
Shut up, oaf.
Saigusa, is that a new joke item of yours?
I made a static generator for my research project!
I see. So it's a toy.
It's science!
Oh yeah, we've got our research projects to think about.
What are you going to do, Masato?
A growth record of my muscles, of course!
Don't make it sound like you're logging
the growth of morning glories.
What about you, Kud?
I know exactly what I'm doing!
That's a rocket, isn't it?
Huh?
Ryachka, been doing well?
Long time no see, Himuro!
She's visiting from our sister school
for her research this summer.
I'm Yuki Himuro, president of science club over there.
You know her?
Yes, she was my roommate when I was in Tevua.
That's quite the interesting project you're working on.
I think so, too!
I'm going to do my summer project on water rockets!
All done!
Did you make this yourself, Ku?
Yup!
This is the first time I've made one,
so there's probably lots of
room for improvement.
That's amazing.
Now we just need to use this to pump in air.
Couldn't we just use a compressor?
It's getting harder and harder.
It's like doing isometrics.
Thank you so much, Inohara!
Looks like it's ready for takeoff.
Cleared for launch!
Starting countdown!
T-minus!
Ignition!
That was amazing, Kud!
It flew that far with just water and air!
That was only a prototype.
I'm going to record data and
keep experimenting to increase its range.
My advice is to start with the shape of the wings.
If you shape them like propellers,
you can make the rocket spin,
which will stabilize its trajectory.
A rocket launching into the blue summer sky,
soaring among white clouds.
That's youth.
Let's all launch our own water rockets.
The one who emerges victorious in the end
will be given the title "Rocket King"!
Mission start!
Rock, paper, scissors!
No!
Wow!
You're so good at this, Haru!
Rin, do your best!
Man, it's hot.
Stop complaining and get moving.
My rockets!
Wafu!
This will keep you from dropping them.
Thank you very much.
I think I heard you say something about rockets.
Are you making water rockets with those?
Do you know about them, miss?
I do, in fact! We're actually
going to make rockets ourselves.
All of you? Amazing!
You must be super good friends!
I don't have friends like that,
so I have to make them by myself.
My name is Kudryavka Noumi.
Would you mind telling me your name, please?
Shiina Arizuki.
Well, Shiina, we're friends now.
Feel free to say no, but would you like
to make water rockets with us?
Yeah!
Wow! Amazing!
They're welcome cookies for you and Himuro.
These are for me?
I could drink this much in my sleep!
It's all soda, though?
Kengo, let's see which of us can down more of these.
Seems it's time for me to put you in your place.
My eyes! My eyes!
You brought that on yourself!
This is fun!
Now then, let's all make rockets
out of the empty bottles!
Would shaping carbon nanotube
like a bottle be cheating?
That's against the rules.
Carbon nanotube?
It's what's used to make real rockets.
Real rockets?!
Yep!
Shiina, what made you want
to make a water rocket?
I want to become an astronaut!
Wafu!
My dream's to become a kosmonavt, too!
My mother is even a kosmonavt.
She's in the International Space Station right now.
Kud?
Don't worry. It's nothing.
Let's get back to work!
Okay, who's going to launch theirs first?
Yes, right here!
This rocket was jointly developed by Sis and me!
The Sexy Sissy!
It's her picture on the rocket,
but Kamikita doesn't have any part in it, right?
Yep, yep.
It's one of my most prized photos.
It'll reveal Komari in quite
the steamy position post launch.
Huh?! When did you take that picture?!
Masato!
Yeah!
Ignition!
No!
Drat. You can't see Komari in
all her shame with how far it's flown.
Don't look at it!
Strelka, don't fetch it!
Okay, next up!
Well then, here's the Naoe,
made by Komari and me.
Why me?
Inohara, if you would, please.
On it!
Once launched, the pictures of Riki and Kyousuke
will hold each other in a sweet embrace.
Huh?!
Wafu?!
I shopped it.
Ignition.
Belka, wait up!
It went farther than the Saigusa-Kurugaya team's.
Looks like we're up next.
Yeah.
Chest!
Fungaaaargh!
You have to launch them with water and air,
so that's against the rules.
What?!
No way!
You idiots.
Whoa!
Hoozawhat?!
We really have to use just water and air?
All right! Next up, it's Riki, Noumi, and Shiina.
Yeah!
All right!
Okay!
Kud, can I become an astronaut?
Becoming a kosmonavt is a big dream.
But as long as you don't give up,
you'll get there for sure.
You really think so?
I do. I believe that will all my heart.
As long as you don't give up.
Kud, we're good to go.
All right!
Ready for takeoff!
Countdown!
Ignition!
My mom's way of finding Polaris is a bit strange.
She'd start from the Summer Triangle.
If you put Altair of Aquila on the other side of the line
connecting Vega of Lyra and Deneb of Cygnus,
that's where you'll find Polaris.
Is something the matter?
You've been looking at me for a while.
I was just thinking about how much you love your mom.
Mom.
Riki, could you listen to me for a bit?
My mom is a really amazing person.
I admired her, and she was my goal.
My mom has been a kosmonavt
for as long as I can remember,
and she has always cheerfully told me
the importance of space exploration.
The reason I wanted to go to space...
The reason I wanted to become a kosmonavt was
because I wanted to see the same things my mom did.
I wanted to see with my own eyes
that the things she loved were fun.
That's why I set my heart on this dream.
But that was a really difficult road to follow.
The further I went, the further away
it felt like my mom was.
Before I knew it, I had stopped dead in my tracks.
I ran away from my mom.
I didn't have the confidence to live up to
her expectations and ran away from Tevua.
It was just that, a dream.
I wanted to keep at it and become a kosmonavt,
thinking that would somehow justify it.
I think being able to talk to someone about your
dreams is pretty impressive on its own.
Riki...
It makes me want to keep cheering you on by your side.
Thank you. Really.
So, um...
Is it okay if I cast a good-luck charm?
A charm?
It's a charm for tying people who
treasure each other together.
We paint our emblems on each other,
and they strengthen the bond between us.
Kud?!
Th-This is very embarrassing,
but also very important and serious.
Will you marry me?
M-M-Marry?! Like, tie the knot?
We're still in school, so I'm not trying
to get ahead of myself or anything,
but that's about my level of conviction.
Okay, I got it.
Let's do it.
Wafu!
Please keep still.
Sorry.
My emblem is filled with curvy waves and mountains.
My mom told me they were gears.
Gears?
I want to be a good set of gears to you.
Wafu.
Kud, stay still.
I'm very sorry.
But...
This is embarrassing.
It tickles.
What kind of pattern are you drawing on me?
Trees, I guess?
That way I'll always be around you,
protecting you from whatever comes.
Riki.
As long as you're with me,
there's nothing I can't do.
My place is by Riki's side.
No matter where that may be.
Kud, wake up.
Wafu?
Kud.
Even in your dream, you're there right next to me.
Riki's just a few inches away from me.
I hope this dream never ends.
Morning, Kud.
Good morning, Riki.
It's pretty quiet.
What happened to everyone?
Oh, right. They all went home.
All summer long,
Riki and I have been alone together.
Riki, let's go get breakfast!
Oh yeah, the cafeteria staff aren't here.
Why don't I make breakfast for you, then?
You would do that?
Of course! I'd be happy to!
I'll come get you once I'm done,
so just hang around in my room until then.
I'm making miso soup for Riki.
It's like we're newlyweds!
You gonna keep running away?
Himuro, you're a strong person,
so there's no way you'll understand how I feel.
I'm trying to be strong, that's all.
So I come off as strong to you as a result.
That's the only reason I can stay here.
You've noticed, haven't you?
That this place is closed off.
You're gonna keep doing this?
Kyousuke said something similar.
And now, Himuro, you're telling me the same thing.
It just means you want someone to tell you.
As long as Riki's with me, I don't need anything else!
That's all I need!
As long as Riki's with me...
As long as he's there...
Riki, breakfast's ready.
Riki?
Riki! Riki!
Riki!
N-No way.
I've always known.
This is a world tailored perfectly to me.
A misguided paradise that I created.
I wanted to become stronger,
even if just within this world.
If I could get just a little better.
Become just a bit stronger.
Perhaps I could take flight one day, too.
No. That's no more than a pipe dream.
I'll never be more than I am.
Kud!
Riki?
I'm coming for you!
Riki? Why?
I'll get these chains off right away!
Riki! Please stop!
I'm fine with this.
I remember everything. I know what happened.
I've already given up because of
the accident on the field trip.
It was a relief to have it all come to
an end without me running away.
But I wanted you, the most important person
in the world to me, to be saved.
So I prayed over and over.
That's why, just knowing you got out fine
was more than enough for me.
It's not enough for me!
We were going to rescue everyone!
Kud, I wanted to become someone strong.
I wanted to understand what it meant to be strong.
I wanted the strength to protect somebody.
And I learned. Learned from all of you.
I learned what it meant from you!
That's why I was able to wake up.
I'm not strong!
I relived all of this over and over.
I kept reliving it all over and over and over
because it was just so much easier,
and I kept running away from reality.
And I'll do it again. I'll relive it all.
I'm weak. I'll never break free of these chains.
I'll only ever be the earthbound Kudryavka.
That's not true at all.
You've been looking for a way to
get stronger this whole time.
Riki.
You've got this. You already know what to do.
I do?
Let's go, Kud!
Riki, where are we going?!
If you want it bad enough,
there's nowhere you can't fly!
Your heart will set you free!
Ku, I've filled it up with water!
Komari?!
It's all set and ready to go.
Nishizono?!
You can count on our
calculations for the wings!
The wind's calm.
It's the perfect time for launch.
Saigusa! Kurugaya!
Inohara! Miyazawa!
We're leaving the rest to you!
Just ten more pumps!
Noumi!
Here's a new mission for you!
Surpass yourself.
Kud, give it all you've got!
You can do it!
Kyousuke.
Rin.
Now, Kud!
The mission's started!
Okay!
10... 9...
8... 7...
6...
You've been running away this whole time.
Can you really get any stronger?
5!
All you've been doing is reliving
this sunny world of yours.
4!
You, the Kudryavka who's bound
by chains and cannot fly.
I want to get stronger! I want to fly!
If you're going to do it,
stick it out to the very end.
Don't just have all the fun yourself.
Let me join in, too.
Ryachka, believe in yourself.
Himuro.
Himuro!
As long as you don't give up,
your wish will come true for sure!
You guys.
3...
2...
1...
Kud, hang in there!
Kud?!
Kud!
Kunya.
1...
Kud!
Yeah!
Riki?!
Riki, wait up!
I can't get stronger by myself!
I can't fly if you aren't there next to me!
Riki!
Kud.
Kud!
Riki?
Is Riki on the other side of the sky?
Has he been watching over me this whole time?
That's right. Riki and I are connected.
Riki. I'm on my way.
Ready for takeoff!
Starting countdown!
T-minus.
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3!
Those chains represent my weakness.
The weakness of seeking strength.
They may appear to be connections,
but they're actually rejections.
I have friends who are there for me.
Whenever I'm feeling lonely or in trouble,
they're always there for me.
And Riki has always been there to support me as well.
2! 1!
Ignition!
Riki?
Riki.
Kud!
Did Ku wake up?!
Little Kud!
Are you feeling okay?!
Kudryavka!
Noumi.
Are you okay?!
Noumi!
Morning, Kud.
Good morning, everyone.
Ku!
Kud!
Hurray! Hurray!
After that long, long dream,
I finally managed to wake up.
I wanted to save Riki,
but he saved me in the end.
I never knew about this place.
I knew I wanted to come here
with you as soon as I found it.
You can see all kinds of stars
here when it gets dark.
If it sounds good to you,
would you like to come stargazing some time?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Riki, would you mind hearing me out on two things?
Two things?
The first is a question I have.
What do you think strength actually is?
I think you've already found that answer yourself.
I don't quite understand it yet.
I don't think you're strong
just because you're not weak.
I think it's just understanding
what it means to be weak.
Wafu?
It's the ability to acknowledge you are weak
and take even just one step forward.
That's what I think it means to be strong.
I see.
How philosophical.
What's the other thing?
The second thing is something I wanted to tell you.
I'm going to work hard to become a kosmonavt.
I think there's going to be a tough road ahead,
and I am bound to lose heart over and over,
but I still want to work towards it.
So you've set your mind to it.
Yep!
A-And...
Is it okay if I add just one more thing?
Riki,
I love you!