We traced the white clouds with our fingers
shiroi kumo wo yubisaki de kakinazoru
And even though we each saw different shapes
omoiegaku katachi wa minna chigatta keredo
The ever-changing sky we gazed upon as we laughed
miteru takasa wa onaji de itsumademo
Was just as far away for us all
kawaritsuzukeru sora wo nagame waratteta
We stretched out our hands and made a circle
ryoute wo hiroge wa wo tsukutte mita
On that summer canvas
natsuiro no kyanbasu ni wa
I could see an infinite future
dokomademo tsuzuku miraiga mieta
I had a dream of us taking flight with tender wings
itaike na tsubasa habataku yume wo mita
Everyone supported me when I was too weak to fly
tobenai yowasa minna ga sasaetekureru
They gave me the courage to open the door and my eyes
tobira wo hirakou me wo akeru yuuki wo
So I'll head beyond the summer
natsu no saki e mukau yo
Because I'm just a little stronger now
sukoshi dake tsuyoku nareta kara
The significance of the strength you taught me
anata ga oshietekureta tsuyosa no imi wa
Is that it realized my dreams
watashi no yume wo musundekureta
It embraced me
dakitometekureta
I had a dream of us taking flight, our wings overlapping
kasaneau tsubasa habataku yume wo mita
You supported me when I was too weak to fly
tobenai yowasa anata ga sasaetekureru
You gave me the courage to open the door and my eyes
tobira wo hirakou me wo akeru yuuki wo
So I'll head beyond the summer
natsu no saki e mukau yo
Because I'm just a little stronger now
sukoshi dake tsuyoku nareta kara