Go to sleep, dear child...
nemure nemure itoshigo
I take in the starlight
hoshi no hikari wo ukete
As my heart longs for you
kimi wo omou kokoro
The distant light of ages past
kotoba ni wa narazu hitori
Penetrates a lonely silence that can't be put into words
shijima ni todoku wa harukeki mukashi no hikari
Can it be far off? Can it be far off?
tookaraji tookaraji
Go to sleep, dear child
nemure nemure itoshigo
You spin around around the violet evening sky
boshi no yozora wo mawaru
As I wish upon you
kimi ni negau tokoro
The intimate light of a moonlit night
kotoba de wa arazu akeki
Resounds through the indescribably pure darkness
yamima ni hibiku wa chikashiki tsukiyo no hikari
Can it be far off? Can it be far off?
tookaraji tookaraji