I chase after it amidst the dazzling heat
mabushii atsusa no naka oikaketa
I reach out my hand towards the blue sky
aoi sora ni te wo nobashiteita
Believing in a promise of someday
itsuka wa to shinji yakusoku wo
My small wings still don't even know how to fly
chiisana hane mada tobikata sae shiranai
So I'll start by walking
dakara mazu arukidasou
Let's head out and search
kimiga mitsumeru manazashi no mukougawa e
For the flicker of summer that passes between the clouds
kumoma wo koeru natsu no mabataki wo
And go beyond where your gaze falls
saa sagashi ni ikou yo
The two of us
koe we
Laugh in unison as we run down the quivering slope
soroete waratte yurameku saka kakeorite
We're aiming for our dreams
ima bokura no yume wo mezashite
As I continue to chase after it amidst the dazzling heat
mabushii atsusa no naka oikaketsuzuketa
After tomorrow, the future, the promise we made that day
ashita wo mirai wo ano hi no yakusoku wo